http://www.simplytoimpress.com/info/privacypolicy

800.779.6177
|
Live Chat
Get your cards in 1-2 days
with Rush or Lightning Printing.
Holiday
Holiday CardsChristmas Photo CardsHoliday Photo CardsHoliday Party InvitationsNew Year's Cards By ThemeBaby's First ChristmasBusiness Holiday CardsCreate Your Own CardFrom the PetFoil Holiday CardsHanukkah CardsHoliday Birth AnnouncementsKwanzaa CardsPandemic Holiday CardsNewReligious Christmas Cards
2020 Holiday CollectionNew
Winter & SpringChinese New Year CardsValentine's Day CardsEaster CardsEID Cards Summer & FallThanksgiving Photo CardsSummer Party InvitationsRosh Hashanah CardsDiwali CardsHalloween Party InvitationsHalloween Photo Cards
Personalized StockingsNew
OrnamentsPersonalized OrnamentsNewLight-Up Glitter OrnamentsNew Stockings Personalized Stockings New Self-Inking StampsAll Stamp DesignsHoliday Stamps
Baby & Kids
Baby AnnouncementsBaby AnnouncementsBoy Baby AnnouncementsGirl Baby AnnouncementsTwin Baby AnnouncementsAdoption AnnouncementsPregnancy AnnouncementsNewHoliday Baby AnnouncementsCreate Your Own Card
Baby Announcements
Birthday InvitationsFirst Birthday InvitationsKids' Birthday InvitationsBoy Birthday InvitationsGirl Birthday InvitationsTwin Birthday InvitationsTeen Birthday Invitations Party SuppliesCustom Yard SignsCustom BannersCoastersCocktail NapkinsDinner Napkins
InvitationsBaby Shower InvitationsBaptism & Christening InvitationsFirst Communion Invitations
StationeryBaby Thank You CardsKids' Thank You CardsStationery For BoysStationery For GirlsStationery For Kids
Wedding
Wedding CardsChange-the-Date Cards NewSave-the-Date CardsSave-the-Date MagnetsWedding Announcements Wedding InvitationsWedding InvitationsRSVP Cards Wedding Sample Kit
Wedding Invitations
Party InvitationsEngagement Party InvitationsBridal Shower InvitationsRehearsal Dinner InvitationsDinner and Cocktail Party InvitationsAnniversary Invitations Reception & PartyCustom Yard SignsCustom BannersCoastersCocktail NapkinsDinner Napkins
Save-the-Date-Cards
StationeryWedding Thank You CardsSelf-Inking StampsStationery for Her
Announcements
Baby Announcements
Baby AnnouncementsBaby AnnouncementsBoy Baby AnnouncementsGirl Baby AnnouncementsBaby Yard SignsBaby BannersTwin Baby AnnouncementsHoliday Baby AnnouncementsAdoption AnnouncementsCreate Your Own Card
Change-the-Date CardsNew
WeddingChange-the-Date CardsNewSave-the-Date CardsWedding AnnouncementsCreate Your Own Card AnnouncementsPregnancy AnnouncementsMoving AnnouncementsMemorial CardsCreate Your Own Card GraduationGraduation AnnouncementsFoil Graduation Cards
Graduation Yard Signs
Celebrations
Birthday PartyFirst Birthday InvitationsKids' Birthday InvitationsTeen Birthday InvitationsAdult Birthday Invitations
Birthday Yard Signs
InvitationsBaby Shower InvitationsBaptism & Christening Invitations Bar Mitzvah InvitationsBat Mitzvah InvitationsBridal Shower InvitationsDinner & Cocktail Party InvitationsGraduation Party InvitationsHousewarming InvitationsParty InvitationsQuinceañera InvitationsVirtual Party InvitationsNewWedding Invitations SeasonalHalloween Party InvitationsHoliday Party InvitationsSummer Party Invitations
Adult Birthday Invitations
Party SuppliesCustom Yard SignsCustom BannersCoastersCocktail Napkins
Business
StationeryBusiness Thank You CardsNewPersonalized StationerySelf-Inking StampsCreate Your Own Card
Self-Inking Stamps
Holiday CardsBusiness Holiday CardsHoliday MagnetsNew Year's CardsChristmas CardsReligious ChristmasHanukkah CardsThanksgiving Cards By IndustryAccountingAttorney & LegalConstructionDentalFinancial ServicesHealthcare & MedicalInsuranceManufacturingMortgage Real Estate
2020 Holiday CollectionNew
PROMOTIONALCustom BannersCustom Yard SignsCustom Face MasksNew CORPORATE PARTYHoliday Party InvitationsRetirement Invitations Custom CoastersCocktail Napkins
Stationery & Gifts
StationerySelf-Inking StampsAll Personalized StationeryStationery for AdultsStationery for HerStationery for HimStationery for KidsCustom Journals
Thank You CardsAll Thank You CardsBirthday Thank You CardsBaby Shower Thank You CardsBusiness Thank You CardsNewGraduation Thank You CardsKids' Thank You CardsMemorial Thank You CardsWedding Thank You Cards
Personalized OrnamentsNew
StockingsPersonalized StockingsNew Top StylesBotanicalCharactersClassic ChristmasLarge NamesPlayfulMonogram
OrnamentsPersonalized OrnamentsNew By TypeCircle OvalHeart Gift Tag RectangleScrollLight-up Glitter
Face Masks
Funny MasksNew
STYLESAnimalsBotanicalCreate Your OwnFacesFloralFunnyHolidaysPhotoNameMonogramPatternRainbowSayingsSportsTeachers & SchoolTie Dye
Photo MasksNew
CUSTOM FACE MASKSKidsFor HerFor HimFor GrandparentsAll Mask Designs
Custom Face MasksNew
Use promo code: 20WISHESHurry, offer ends Dec 10th*
Privacy Policy
Welcome! We (“we,” “us” or “our”) are the developer of the services offered (the “Services”) via our websites and mobile applications (each, a “Destination”). As such, we want to provide you with this, our privacy policy. Your privacy is extremely important to us. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy with respect to personally identifiable data and other information that is collected from visitors to a Destination and users of the Services.
In order to make your visits to our Destinations both enjoyable and responsive, we collect certain information when you visit us online. Your use of our Destinations and/or the Services confirms your acceptance of this privacy policy and your agreement to be bound by it.
How Your Information is Collected
When you place an order on a Destination or by using the Services, you may be prompted to provide (and we may collect) certain types of information, such as your name, postal address (for shipping and billing), e-mail address, telephone number, financial information (such as your credit card number) and other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, transaction information, device information and product and service preferences. We also may collect the e-mail addresses of customers who communicate with us via e-mail and those who provide their e-mail address when joining a mailing list. In addition, we may collect personally identifiable information that is provided to us by visitors to a Destination or who use the Services in connection with contest participations, survey information and member account registrations.
We may collect aggregate or non-identifiable (anonymous) information from all visitors to a Destination and/or users of the Services, regardless of whether they place an order with us, volunteer such information, communicate with us, join a mailing list or otherwise (such as language, zip code, unique device identifier and location). We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to a Destination and Services, the number of visitors to each page of a Destination , the number of users of the Services, the domain names of our visitors’ internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with Destinations and Services. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners, or disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe a Destination and/or the Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
We may also collect information about you from commercially available sources. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information that we may collect from these sources may be used along with the information that we collect from you when you visit a Destination or use the Services.
Cookies and Other Information Gathering Tools
Like many Destinations, we use “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that reside on your computer and identify you as a unique user. Cookies allow us to, among other things, measure activity on a Destination or through the
Services and to personalize your experience. For example, cookies enable us to remember your viewing preferences without requiring you to re-type a user name and password. Cookies also allow us to track your status or progress when ordering products and services from us. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions. However, if you reject or delete cookies you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features on a Destination or the Services. We also use other common information gathering tools such as web beacons and embedded web links.
Children’s Information
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, and we do not target any Destination or any of the Services, to children under the age of eighteen (18).
Our Terms of Use prohibit individuals younger than eighteen (18) years old from accessing or using the Services in any manner.
How We Use Your Information
We use your personally identifiable information to fulfill purchases that you make through a Destination and/or the Services, for marketing purposes, and to provide service and support.
Unless you opt-out in accordance with the procedure set forth below, if you provide us with your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about products, services and upcoming events. We reserve the right to share this information with affiliates and other reputable organizations for service, support and marketing purposes, and so that they may offer products and services that we believe will be attractive to our customers and to those who have subscribed to a mailing list.
In addition, we may share your information with third parties in order to: (i) respond to the requests of police and governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order, (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect our rights or (iv) protect the personal safety of our personnel and third parties. We may also share or transfer your information with third parties for business reasons, such as in the context of the sale or merger of our company or business.
When you provide us with your credit card information we redirect that information to certain third parties only for the purpose of payment processing in accordance with their own privacy and security policies.
Third-Party Ad Servers
We may use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf on a Destination and/or through the Services. Such providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to a Destination and use of the Services. They may use information about your visits to a Destination or use of the Services to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process (such as your name, phone number or postal or email address).
The NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) allows for the central opting out of all of its members’ cookies from a single opt-out page. If you prefer not to receive certain behavioral advertising, please click on the following link: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
If you delete your cookies, use a different browser or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.
We also work with third parties to monitor certain pages of Destinations and the Services for the purpose of reporting website traffic and other advertising statistics. These third parties may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about the visitors to a Destination or the users of the Services. However, no personally identifiable information is transferred to these third parties.
Links to Third Party Websites
A Destination and the Services may contain links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. We do not control those websites or make any representations or warranties about their use or the third-party policies that govern such use. Any personal information that is obtained by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites.
Integrating Third-Party Services within the Services
One of the special features of the Services is that they allow you to enable various online third party services, such as social media and social networking services (“Third-Party Services”), to be directly integrated into your experience. To take advantage of this feature, we may ask you to provide us your username and password for the relevant Third-Party Services. By enabling such Third-Party Services, you are allowing us to pass your log-in information to these service providers for this purpose. When you add a Third-Party Service account to the Services, we will collect your login information and other relevant information necessary to enable the Services to access that Third-Party Service and your data contained within that Third-Party Service. However, please remember that the manner in which Third-Party Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and we will have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third-Party Service that may be enabled within the Services.
Security
We maintain reasonable and appropriate security procedures, but we can’t guarantee that your information will be secure in every circumstance.
Notices
If we are required to provide you with notice of a particular event or incident, we will send you such notice by mail, email or telephone.
Changing Your Information
If you believe that you have provided us with information that is incorrect or that needs to be updated you may contact us, in the case you are using a mobile app, via the Contact Us option on the drawer menu in the upper left corner of the screen or, in the case you are using a website, via the Contact Us page.
Opt-Out / Unsubscribe
You can access a Destination or the Services without providing any personally identifiable information. However, if you do not provide any personally identifiable information you may not be able to use certain features of a Destination or the Services (such as registering, opening an account or making purchases). If you would like to discontinue receiving marketing-related e-mails and opt-out of certain uses of your personally identifiable information by us, please contact us, in the case you are using a mobile app, via the Contact Us option on the drawer menu in the upper left corner of the screen or, in the case you are using a website, via the Contact Us page.
Exclusions
This Privacy Policy will not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us through a Destination or the Services or through any other means, including, without limitation, information posted to any public areas of a Destination or the Services, any feedback or ideas for new products or modifications to existing offerings, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information will be deemed to be non-confidential and we will be free to use, reproduce, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation, or compensation or attribution to you.
Other Terms and Conditions
Your access to and use of a Destination and the Services are subject to the Terms of Use.
How to Contact Us
If you feel that we are not following this Privacy Policy, you wish to be removed from a mailing list, or you have any questions about a Destination or the Services, you may contact us, in the case you are using a mobile app, via the Contact Us option on the drawer menu in the upper left corner of the screen or, in the case you are using a website, via the Contact Us page.
Effective Date
This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 15, 2019. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, effective immediately upon its posting. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically check this Destination or access this Privacy Policy through the Services. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of a Destination or the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy will indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.
* Sale ends 11:59:59 pm Pacific Time on December 10, 2020.* $3 2-day shipping valid for cards only, other products may require 1 or 2 additional days in transit. Without promo code, the current sale is 35% off.
About Us
Our Story
What Makes Us Different
Customer Reviews
Affiliate Program
Press Releases
Supplier Code of Conduct
Customer Service
© 2003-2020, Simply to Impress. All rights reserved.
From Wirecutter. © 2018 The Wirecutter, Inc. All rights reserved. Used under License.
Simply to Impress is committed to creating an inclusive experience for people with disabilities. If you need assistance, please call 1-800-779-6177.
IMPORTANT LEGAL NOTICE: This website and its entire contents, including but not limited to all artwork,
design and text, are protected under all United States and International Copyright Laws. It is unlawful
to reproduce, transmit, print, or distribute either the form or content of any portion of this website
without the expressed written consent of SimplytoImpress.
To inquire about these policies please Contact Us.
iPad is a trademark of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries.
This card is eligible for two types of expedited service (at an additional charge):
- Rush Service - If ordered before 7 PM PST today [details]
1 day to print + overnight shipping
- Lightning Service - If ordered before 11 AM PST today [details]
0 days to print + overnight shipping
